[
    {
        "background": "a 44 years old male with a recent STEMI with DES placed in LAD. He experienced bilateral arm tightness and uneasiness, but no dyspnea, nausea, diaphoresis, chest pain, or jaw radiation. EKG showed no STEMI. He has a history of CAD, dyslipidemia, and hypertension. Stress Echo showed excellent exercise capacity with no anginal symptoms or ischemic EKG changes. He was pain-free on admission and was started on lisinopril at discharge.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "B": "Atorvastatin",
            "C": "Heparin",
            "D": "Metoprolol Succinate",
            "E": "Clopidogrel",
            "F": "Lisinopril",
            "G": "Aspirin",
            "H": "Nitroglycerin"
        },
        "correct_answer": "EGBDF",
        "hadm_id": "23071013",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 1
    },
    {
        "background": "a 50 years old male with anxiety, hypertension, and recurrent pancreatitis. He was admitted for ERCP with sphincterotomy due to common bile duct sludge and pancreas divisum, which were thought to be the cause of his recurrent pancreatitis. The procedure was successful, and he was kept NPO with IV fluids and pain control. His condition improved, and he underwent laparoscopic cholecystectomy. At discharge, he was stable, ambulating, and voiding independently. He was advised to follow up in the Acute Care Surgery clinic.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Testosterone Cypionate",
            "B": "OxycoDONE (Immediate Release)",
            "C": "Ondansetron",
            "D": "Lactated Ringers",
            "E": "Prochlorperazine",
            "F": "Bystolic (nebivolol)",
            "G": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "H": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%  Flush",
            "I": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "J": "Acetaminophen",
            "K": "Acetaminophen IV",
            "L": "Heparin",
            "M": "Escitalopram Oxalate",
            "N": "Lorazepam",
            "O": "Chloraseptic Throat Spray"
        },
        "correct_answer": "MNFAJB",
        "hadm_id": "22020219",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 2
    },
    {
        "background": "a gentleman with a history of an incidentally identified mesenteric cyst and acute appendicitis. He underwent an open appendectomy and removal of the mesenteric cyst. Post-operatively, he was stable, with normal renal function and no signs of infection. He was discharged in good condition, tolerating a regular diet, ambulating, and with well-controlled pain.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Ondansetron",
            "B": "Potassium Chl",
            "C": "Docusate Sodium",
            "D": "LR",
            "E": "SW",
            "F": "0.9% Sodium Chloride",
            "G": "Magnesium Sulfate",
            "H": "Morphine Sulfate",
            "I": "5% Dextrose",
            "J": "Oxycodone-Acetaminophen",
            "K": "NS",
            "L": "MetRONIDAZOLE (FLagyl)",
            "M": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "N": "Metoclopramide",
            "O": "Potassium Chloride",
            "P": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "Q": "Heparin",
            "R": "Ciprofloxacin IV"
        },
        "correct_answer": "CJ",
        "hadm_id": "25690768",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 3
    },
    {
        "background": "a female diagnosed with severe aortic stenosis years ago, recently experiencing dyspnea on exertion, palpitations, and fatigue. She underwent a diagnostic right and left heart catheterization, revealing severely elevated biventricular filling pressures, depressed left ventricular function, and marked pulmonary hypertension. She is admitted for diuresis and surgical evaluation for aortic valve replacement. Her coronary arteries are normal, and she has no significant carotid artery stenosis. She was sent home with instructions to monitor her weight and symptoms.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Furosemide",
            "B": "Senna",
            "C": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "D": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "E": "Docusate Sodium",
            "F": "D5 1/2NS",
            "G": "Heparin"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "hadm_id": "29364896",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 4
    },
    {
        "background": "a male with a history of cocaine use, alcohol abuse, emphysema, and GERD, presented with chest pain for 1 month. The pain was not worsened by exercise or alleviated by rest. He had occasional sweating, shortness of breath, and dizziness. In the ED, he was given ASA, nitroglycerin, and morphine, with negative cardiac enzymes. CXR showed moderate bronchiectasis and early pneumonia. He has a history of asthma, depression, anxiety, hypercholesterolemia, hypertension, and substance use. He expressed interest in substance abuse treatment. He also had concerns about STD risk and was advised to follow up for HIV testing. He has chronic lower back pain and scrotal pain, with follow-up arranged. His hypertension and hyperlipidemia were not active issues during his stay.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Albuterol Sulfate",
            "B": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "C": "Aspirin",
            "D": "Ranitidine",
            "E": "Acetaminophen",
            "F": "Docusate Sodium",
            "G": "Albuterol 0.083% Neb Soln",
            "H": "Heparin"
        },
        "correct_answer": "DCA",
        "hadm_id": "24647107",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 5
    },
    {
        "background": "A male patient with a history of renal cell carcinoma, prostate cancer with metastasis to bone, and colon cancer presented with confusion, headaches, lightheadedness, and dizziness worsening over the past 3 weeks. He underwent a posterior fossa craniotomy for tumor resection and was treated for cerebral edema. The patient was evaluated by Neuro-oncology and cleared for discharge.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Sodium Chloride",
            "B": "Morphine Sulfate",
            "C": "LevETIRAcetam",
            "D": "Diazepam",
            "E": "Glucagon",
            "F": "OxyCODONE (Immediate Release)",
            "G": "Dexamethasone",
            "H": "Famotidine",
            "I": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%  Flush",
            "J": "Atorvastatin",
            "K": "Lidocaine Jelly 2% (Glydo)",
            "L": "Labetalol",
            "M": "Glucose Gel",
            "N": "HydrALAZINE",
            "O": "Docusate Sodium",
            "P": "Dextrose 50%",
            "Q": "Acetaminophen",
            "R": "Insulin",
            "S": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%",
            "T": "Senna",
            "U": "Metoprolol Succinate XL",
            "V": "Neutra-Phos",
            "W": "Heparin",
            "X": "Methocarbamol"
        },
        "correct_answer": "QGOHXFTAJU",
        "hadm_id": "21501880",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 6
    },
    {
        "background": "a woman with a history of pelvic organ prolapse, stress urinary incontinence, hypercholesterolemia, osteopenia, and gestational diabetes. She underwent a robotic-assisted supracervical hysterectomy, bilateral salpingo-oophorectomy, sacral cervico-colpopexy, transvaginal tape urethral sling, posterior colporrhaphy, and cystoscopy. Her post-operative course was uncomplicated, and she was discharged in stable condition.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Lactated Ringers",
            "B": "Ibuprofen",
            "C": "Docusate Sodium",
            "D": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "E": "Oxycodone-Acetaminophen",
            "F": "Ketorolac",
            "G": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush"
        },
        "correct_answer": "CBE",
        "hadm_id": "29889162",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 7
    },
    {
        "background": "a male with a history of hypertension, dyslipidemia, and family history of early coronary artery disease who presented with chest pain and was diagnosed with NSTEMI. He underwent successful PTCA/stenting of the mid circumflex with a drug-eluting stent. The patient was chest pain free upon discharge and had a history of hypothyroidism. He was transferred for catheterization after a positive stress test and elevated troponins. The patient was discharged with post-MI teaching and arrangements to see a new cardiologist.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Ondansetron",
            "B": "Heparin Sodium",
            "C": "Lorazepam",
            "D": "Valsartan",
            "E": "Metoprolol Tartrate",
            "F": "5% Dextrose",
            "G": "Crestor",
            "H": "Atorvastatin",
            "I": "Atropine Sulfate",
            "J": "Levothyroxine",
            "K": "Potassium Chloride",
            "L": "Aspirin",
            "M": "Atenolol",
            "N": "Acetaminophen",
            "O": "Levothyroxine Sodium",
            "P": "Nitroglycerin SL",
            "Q": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "R": "Ranitidine",
            "S": "Clopidogrel",
            "T": "Heparin"
        },
        "correct_answer": "DMJLSGR",
        "hadm_id": "28312622",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 8
    },
    {
        "background": "A patient with a history of dyslipidemia, hypothyroidism, and breast cancer presented with chest pain. The patient experienced intermittent chest pain over three months, worsening recently, and was referred to the ED. Initial evaluation showed elevated cardiac enzymes and ST depressions on EKG, consistent with a 99% blockage of the RCA, which was stented. The patient was diagnosed with Type I NSTEMI/ACS and has a right carotid bruit. The patient underwent successful rotational atherectomy and stenting of the RCA. The patient has a family history of coronary artery disease, with both parents having undergone CABG.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Metoprolol Succinate XL",
            "B": "Heparin Sodium",
            "C": "Aspirin",
            "D": "PredniSONE",
            "E": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%",
            "F": "Atorvastatin",
            "G": "Metoprolol Tartrate",
            "H": "Clopidogrel",
            "I": "5% Dextrose",
            "J": "Nitroglycerin SL",
            "K": "Atropine Sulfate",
            "L": "DiphenhydrAMINE",
            "M": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "N": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "O": "Heparin",
            "P": "Levothyroxine Sodium"
        },
        "correct_answer": "PCFHA",
        "hadm_id": "23597440",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 9
    },
    {
        "background": "a female with a history of infertility, endometriosis, and mild asthma, presented with severe right lower quadrant pain and an enlarged right ovary. She underwent urgent surgery for a hemorrhagic right ovarian cyst, hemoperitoneum, and pelvic endometriosis. Post-operative recovery was uncomplicated, and she was discharged in stable condition.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Ibuprofen",
            "B": "Lactated Ringers",
            "C": "OxycoDONE (Immediate Release)",
            "D": "Ascorbic Acid",
            "E": "Oxycodone-Acetaminophen (5mg-325mg)",
            "F": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "G": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "H": "Ferrous Sulfate",
            "I": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%  Flush",
            "J": "Docusate Sodium",
            "K": "Acetaminophen",
            "L": "Acetaminophen IV"
        },
        "correct_answer": "JKCHAD",
        "hadm_id": "25171352",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 10
    },
    {
        "background": "a woman with no significant past medical history presented with typical chest pain and ECG findings concerning for STEMI. Cardiac catheterization revealed 99% occlusion of the distal RCA and 70% proximal RCA narrowing, for which 2 drug-eluting stents were placed. She was also noted to have mild-moderate disease in the LAD and LCx. TTE revealed normal left ventricular cavity size with very mild regional systolic dysfunction and LVEF 51%. Additional CAD workup revealed elevated hemoglobin A1c of 10.9%. The patient was discharged on dual-antiplatelet therapy, high-intensity statin, metoprolol, and lisinopril. She was advised to follow up with her PCP for type 2 diabetes management and to continue smoking cessation.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Metoprolol Tartrate",
            "B": "Glucose Gel",
            "C": "Atorvastatin",
            "D": "Metoprolol Succinate XL",
            "E": "Lisinopril",
            "F": "Ramelteon",
            "G": "Influenza Vaccine Quadrivalent",
            "H": "Glucagon",
            "I": "LORazepam",
            "J": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "K": "Dextrose 50%",
            "L": "Heparin",
            "M": "TiCAGRELOR",
            "N": "Aspirin",
            "O": "Insulin"
        },
        "correct_answer": "NCEDM",
        "hadm_id": "22551558",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 11
    },
    {
        "background": "A young adult female with no past medical history presented with several weeks of headaches and transient visual obscurations, found to have papilledema on fundoscopic exam. Her headaches were described as bifrontal and pounding, worsened by cough or valsalva, and not responsive to ibuprofen or acetaminophen. Lumbar puncture showed elevated opening pressure and lymphocytic pleocytosis. MRI was benign. The patient was treated for secondary intracranial hypertension with acetazolamide. Follow-up with neuro-ophthalmology was planned.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%",
            "B": "Docusate Sodium",
            "C": "Ondansetron",
            "D": "LORazepam",
            "E": "Acetaminophen",
            "F": "Ibuprofen",
            "G": "Lidocaine 1%",
            "H": "AcetaZOLamide",
            "I": "Heparin"
        },
        "correct_answer": "HC",
        "hadm_id": "24122478",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 12
    },
    {
        "background": "A woman admitted with substernal chest pain, found to have ST elevations and underwent cardiac catheterization with stenting of the RCA. She has a history of type II diabetes mellitus, osteoporosis, glaucoma, spinal stenosis, macular degeneration, dementia, and is hard of hearing. Echocardiogram showed preserved biventricular systolic function with elevated filling pressures. She was stable post-procedure and discharged with a treatment plan for her conditions.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Memantine",
            "B": "Aspirin",
            "C": "Lisinopril",
            "D": "Timolol Maleate",
            "E": "Metoprolol Tartrate",
            "F": "Namenda",
            "G": "Atorvastatin",
            "H": "Alendronate",
            "I": "Cyanocobalamin",
            "J": "Clopidogrel",
            "K": "Actos"
        },
        "correct_answer": "BJECGHIFDK",
        "hadm_id": "27791786",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 13
    },
    {
        "background": "a male heavy smoker with acute onset of left lower extremity pain due to thrombosis in the distal popliteal into the tibioperoneal trunk. Underwent LLE angiogram with lysis catheter placement with resolution of clot. Discharged on oral anticoagulation with xarelto for six months. Follow-up required with vascular surgery and cardiology/vascular medicine.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Heparin Sodium",
            "B": "OxyCODONE (Immediate Release)",
            "C": "Acetaminophen",
            "D": "Alteplase",
            "E": "0.9% Sodium Chloride",
            "F": "Aspirin",
            "G": "Lactated Ringers",
            "H": "5% Dextrose",
            "I": "Influenza Vaccine Quadrivalent",
            "J": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "K": "D5 1/2NS",
            "L": "Rivaroxaban"
        },
        "correct_answer": "CFL",
        "hadm_id": "29365163",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 14
    },
    {
        "background": "a 63 years old female with a history of pelvic organ prolapse, who underwent a robotic sacral colpopexy and cystoscopy. Her post-operative course was uncomplicated, and she was discharged in stable condition. She had a history of a vaginal hysterectomy, uterosacral ligament suspension, and posterior repair. The patient reported bothersome symptoms from her prolapse, negatively impacting her quality of life, and desired surgical management. Her physical exam showed a protruding vaginal vault, and she was voiding spontaneously with minimal spotting at discharge.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Ondansetron",
            "B": "Ibuprofen",
            "C": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "D": "Lactated Ringers",
            "E": "Ketorolac",
            "F": "Docusate Sodium",
            "G": "Hydrochlorothiazide",
            "H": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "I": "Acetaminophen",
            "J": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush"
        },
        "correct_answer": "GBFIC",
        "hadm_id": "23073140",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 15
    },
    {
        "background": "A male with a history of depression, BPH, and hepatitis C presented with a left closed bicondylar tibial plateau fracture after a collision with another bicyclist. He underwent knee-spanning external fixation and open reduction internal fixation of the right tibial plateau. The patient was discharged to rehab with instructions for DVT prophylaxis and follow-up care.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Morphine Sulfate",
            "B": "Zolpidem Tartrate",
            "C": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "D": "Bisacodyl",
            "E": "Lactated Ringers",
            "F": "CeFAZolin",
            "G": "Senna",
            "H": "Acetaminophen",
            "I": "Iso-Osmotic Dextrose",
            "J": "Ketorolac",
            "K": "Tetanus-DiphTox-Acellular Pertuss (Adacel)",
            "L": "Ramelteon",
            "M": "Influenza Vaccine Quadrivalent",
            "N": "Ondansetron",
            "O": "Enoxaparin Sodium",
            "P": "Docusate Sodium",
            "Q": "OxyCODONE (Immediate Release)",
            "R": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "S": "Tamsulosin",
            "T": "BuPROPion (Sustained Release)",
            "U": "Vitamin D"
        },
        "correct_answer": "HPONQTS",
        "hadm_id": "28842082",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 16
    },
    {
        "background": "A female patient with no past medical history presented with pain in the lateral aspect of her right knee. MRI showed degeneration and a small tear in the lateral meniscus. She underwent an arthroscopic lateral meniscectomy and distal femoral varus producing osteotomy. The procedure was well-tolerated without complications. Post-operatively, she was placed in a brace and progressed well with physical therapy. Her pain was well controlled with oral pain medications, and her labs remained stable throughout her hospitalization.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Ondansetron",
            "B": "Potassium Chloride",
            "C": "Calcium Carbonate",
            "D": "Enoxaparin Sodium",
            "E": "Oxycodone",
            "F": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "G": "Aluminum-Magnesium Hydrox.-Simethicone",
            "H": "Aspirin, Buffered",
            "I": "Vitamin D",
            "J": "Senna",
            "K": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "L": "CefazoLIN",
            "M": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "N": "Acetaminophen",
            "O": "Docusate Sodium",
            "P": "Multivitamins",
            "Q": "Ferrous Sulfate"
        },
        "correct_answer": "EDOHJ",
        "hadm_id": "29365343",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 17
    },
    {
        "background": "a 73 years old male with a history of diabetes mellitus, peripheral artery disease, and chronic kidney disease, among other conditions. He was admitted for pre-hydration prior to an endovascular procedure due to baseline renal dysfunction. He underwent a right lower extremity angiogram with posterior tibial angioplasty and stent, which was without complication. He was discharged with plans to follow up with a duplex in a month.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Docusate Sodium",
            "B": "0.9% Sodium Chloride",
            "C": "Humalog",
            "D": "Magnesium Sulfate",
            "E": "Vitamin E",
            "F": "Omeprazole",
            "G": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "H": "Ferrous Sulfate",
            "I": "Saccharomyces boulardii",
            "J": "Doxycycline Hyclate",
            "K": "Simvastatin",
            "L": "Glucagon",
            "M": "Ascorbic Acid",
            "N": "Fish Oil",
            "O": "Aspirin",
            "P": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "Q": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "R": "Allopurinol",
            "S": "Glargine",
            "T": "Dextrose 50%",
            "U": "Carvedilol",
            "V": "Furosemide",
            "W": "Bag",
            "X": "Heparin",
            "Y": "Clopidogrel",
            "Z": "Insulin",
            "a": "Vitamin B Complex"
        },
        "correct_answer": "UJVSCFKMHEaINYRO",
        "hadm_id": "21497645",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 18
    },
    {
        "background": "a 62 years old male with recurrent RUQ pain, elevated transaminases, and total bilirubin. Underwent ERCP with sphincterotomy and biopsies, treated with antibiotics and fluid resuscitation. Discharged after improvement, advised to follow up for pathology results and with GI. Declined cholecystectomy. No aspirin, Plavix, NSAIDs, or Coumadin for 5 days. History of suspected choledocholithiasis, no prior abdominal surgery, and denies family history of cancer, liver, or GI disease.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "MetRONIDAZOLE (FLagyl)",
            "B": "Ondansetron",
            "C": "Senna",
            "D": "Lactated Ringers",
            "E": "HYDROmorphone (Dilaudid)",
            "F": "0.9% Sodium Chloride (Mini Bag Plus)",
            "G": "Sodium Chloride 0.9%  Flush",
            "H": "Acetaminophen",
            "I": "Docusate Sodium",
            "J": "D5 1/2NS",
            "K": "Heparin",
            "L": "Ciprofloxacin HCl",
            "M": "Ampicillin-Sulbactam"
        },
        "correct_answer": "LA",
        "hadm_id": "24123939",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 19
    },
    {
        "background": "a 61 years old male with a history of SVT, hypertension, MVP, and hyperlipidemia who presented with worsening chest pain and a positive stress test indicating unstable angina. Coronary angiography revealed one vessel coronary artery disease and left main disease. The patient has a normal left ventricular ejection fraction and wall motion. He was scheduled for surgical intervention. The patient has a history of depression and PUD. Family history includes various cancers but no early MI or sudden cardiac death.",
        "discharge_medications_options": {
            "A": "Senna",
            "B": "Simvastatin",
            "C": "0.9% Sodium Chloride",
            "D": "Metoprolol Succinate",
            "E": "Clopidogrel",
            "F": "Atropine Sulfate",
            "G": "Influenza Virus Vaccine",
            "H": "Effexor XR",
            "I": "Sodium Chloride 0.9% Flush",
            "J": "Aspirin",
            "K": "1/2 NS",
            "L": "Docusate Sodium",
            "M": "Heparin",
            "N": "Venlafaxine XR"
        },
        "correct_answer": "BDHJ",
        "hadm_id": "29888423",
        "question": "Which medications should be prescribed to the patient at discharge?",
        "index": 20
    }
]